Kiley, Dan (Dan Urban), 1912-2004. Papers of Dan Kiley: An Inventory.
Kiley, Dan (Dan Urban), 1912-2004. Papers of Dan Kiley: An Inventory.
- Landscape Architecture Drawings, / Date(s): ca. 1941 - ca. 1995; 0000; / Quantity: ca. 483 tubes; 128 folders; 2 boxes / Medium: Mixed / Support: Mixed
  - Addenda / Exhibition Materials, / Date(s): 1920ca.-1997; Folder: A005; / Quantity: 14 / Dimensions: <76x55cm. / Medium: Photographs / Support: Paper
Health facilities / Landscaping plans 0874, 0979
Health facilities / Master plans 0807
High schools / Site plans 0591
Highways / Landscaping plans 0957
Highways / Landscaping plans 01016
Hillside architecture / Landscaping plans 0918
Hillside architecture / Sketches 01283
Historic buildings / Architectural drawings 0048
Historic districts / Landscaping plans 0457, 0922
Historic districts / Site plans 0528
Historic houses / Landscaping plans 01028, 0903
Historic houses / Survey plans 05043
Historic landscapes / Landscaping plans 01028, 0903
Historic sites / Landscaping plans 0457
Horse racetracks / Landscaping plans 01155
Horticultural societies / Master plans 0960
Hospitals / Landscaping plans 01065, 0979
Hotels / Landscaping plans 0887, 0922
Hotels / Master plans 01255
Housing / Site plans 0666, 0848
Housing complexes / Landscaping plans 0527
Housing developments / Site plans 0332
Housing projects / Landscaping plans 0239
Housing projects / Site plans 0042
Indian reservations / Site plans 0942
Industrial buildings / Landscaping plans 0820, 0934, 0936
Industrial buildings / Site plan 0937
Industrial complexes / Landscaping plans 0705
Industrial complexes / Site plans 0421, 0422
Industrial landscapes / Landscaping plans 0500
Industrial landscapes / Site plans 0421, 0422
Industrial structures / Landscaping plans 0874
Infirmaries / Landscaping plans 0601
Inns / Construction drawings 0484
Inns / Landscaping plans 01259
Inns / Landscaping plans 0481
Inns / Master plans 0944
Interchanges / Landscaping plans 0675
Interior design / Landscaping plans 01259
International organizations / Architectural drawings 0849
Irrigation systems / Planting plans 0536
Islands / Landscaping plans 01060, 0903
Islands / Master plans 0951
Junior high schools / Site plans 0591
Lakes / Landscaping plans 01273, 0472
Lakes / Master plans 01119, 0196
Landscape gardens / Landscaping plans 0396
Landscape gardens / Planting plans 0459
Landscape gardens / Sketches 01240
Law schools / Landscaping plans 0451, 0840
Legislative buildings / Landscaping plans 01253
Libraries (Buildings) / Architectural drawings 0677
Libraries (Buildings) / Landscaping plans 01191
Lighthouses / Landscaping plans 0684, 0723
Lodges / Architectural drawings 0180
Low-cost housing / Landscaping plans 0239
Magazines (Periodicals) / Site plans 0189
Malls / Landscaping plans 01266
Mandalas / Master plans 0816
Mansions / Sketches 01283
Manufacturing / Landscaping plans 05041, 0508, 0539, 0578
Manufacturing / Master plans 0586
Manufacturing / Planting plans 0592
Marine parks / Landscaping plans 01079, 0721, 0723
Master plans / Landscaping plans 0881
Mausoleums / Planting plans 0385
Medical centers / Landscaping plans 0874
Medical centers / Master plans 0807
Medical schools / Landscaping plans 0795
Memorials / Landscaping plans 0693
Memorials / Planting plans 0385
Mental health facilities / Landscaping plans 0984
Mental health facilities / Master plans 0991
Mental health facilities / Site plans 0928
Middle schools / Landscaping plans 01227
Military academies / Landscaping plans 0415
Military academies / Landscaping plans 0718
Military bases / Master plans 0926
Mixed use developments / Landscaping plans 0885, 0922
Mixed-use developments / Master plans 01254, 01256
Mixed-use developments / Master plans 01255, 0816
Model houses / Planting plans 0270
Models (Representations) / Landscaping planss 01017
Modernist / Landscaping plans 0396
Motion picture studios / Preliminary drawings 01258
Mountains / Landscaping plans 0671, 0858
Mountains / Master plans 0811
Mountains / Site plans 0827, 0865
Multi-purpose buildings / Landscaping plans 0924
Municipal utilities / Landscaping plans 0589
Museums / Landscaping plans 01053, 01074, 01106, 01159
Museums / Landscaping planss 01017
Museums / Master plans 01049, 01113
Museums / Preliminary drawings 01029, 01032
Museums / Working drawings 01033
National collections / Site plans 0909
National forests / Landscaping plans 0534
National historic landmarks / Landscaping plans 0134
National holidays / Landscaping plans 0957
National monuments / Landscaping plans 0134, 0457
National museums (Buildings) / Site plans 0909
National organizations / Landscaping plans 0581, 0638
National parks / Landscaping plans 01266, 0134, 0457, 0534
Natural history / Site plans 0871
Nature centers / Site plans 0871
New Urbanism / Architect's drawings 01260
New Urbanism / Landscaping plans 01248
Nonprofit organizations / Architectural drawings 0596, 0677
Nonprofit organizations / Landscaping plans 0476
Non-profit organizations / Landscaping plans 0437
Occupational safety / Landscaping plans 0874
Office buildings / Landscaping plans 01042, 01054, 01057, 01158, 01178, 01212, 0766, 0946, 0947
Office buildings / Master plans 01186
Office buildings / Planting plans 0998
Office complexes / Architect's drawings 01260
Office complexes / Master plans 0879
Office parks / Landscaping plans 01143, 01147, 0660
Office parks / Site plans 0814
Officers (Administrators) / Architectural drawings 0596
Officers (Administrators) / Landscaping plans 0599
Office towers / Landscaping plans 01158, 0946
Official residences / Architectural drawings 0596
Official residences / Landscaping plans 0469, 0529, 0599, 0775
Olympic villages / Landscaping plans 05030
Open air exhibitions / Landscaping plans 01074, 01106
Open air theaters / Site plans 0709
Orchards / Master plans 01252
Orphanages / Landscaping plans 0476
Outdoor sculpture / Landscaping plans 01072
Overlooks / Landscaping plans 0691
Parking / Landscaping plans 0705
Parking / Site plans 0701
Parking garages / Landscaping plans 0883
Parking lots / Landscaping plans 0608
Parking lots / Preliminary drawings 0943
Parking lots / Site plans 0773, 0928
Parks / Landscaping plans 01230
Parks (recreation areas) / Master plans 0926
Parks (Recreation areas) / Comprehensive plans 0717
Parks (Recreation areas) / Landscaping plans 01060, 01079, 0506, 0625, 0655, 0681, 0682, 0686
Parks (Recreation areas) / Master plans 01025, 01119, 0875, 0954
Parks (Recreation areas) / Site plans 01233, 0746
Passenger terminals / Schematic drawings 01193
Pavilions (Garden structures) / Landscaping plans 0472
Pavilions (Garden structures) / Planting plans 0459
Paving / Site plans 01022
Pedestrian malls / Landscaping plans 0885
Performing arts centers / Landscaping plans 0661
Performing arts centers / Planting plans 0478
Performing arts centers / Preliminary drawings 0733
Piers (Marine landings) / Landscaping plans 01273
Plantations / Landscaping plans 01209, 0932
Planters (Containers) / Planting plans 0478
Playgrounds / Landscaping plans 0725, 0726
Plazas / Landscaping plans 01042, 01054, 01062, 01210, 0691, 0693, 0766, 0885, 0931, 0962
Plazas / Master plans 01171, 01245
Plazas / Preliminary drawings 01095
Polo clubs / Landscaping plans 01248
Polytechnics / Landscaping plans 0921
Polytechnics / Master plans 0502
Pools / Landscaping plans 0842
Porches / Detail drawings 05012, 05013
Ports / Master plans 0913
Prefabrication / Landscaping plans 0155
Preliminary drawings / Landscaping plans 01213, 0661
Preparatory schools / Architectural drawings 0180
Preparatory schools / Landscaping plans 01073
Preparatory schools / Master plans 0614
Presidential libraries (Buildings) / Sketches 01003
Private gardens / Landscaping plans 0396
Private libraries / Landscaping plans 01191
Private schools / Landscaping plans 0542
Private schools / Master plans 0614
Projects / Preliminary drawings 01258
Promenades (Walkways) / Master plans 0976
Psychiatric clinics / Master plans 0991
Psychiatric hospitals / Landscaping plans 0984
Psychiatric hospitals / Site plans 0928
Public buildings / Landscaping plans 05045
Public buildings / Master plans 01005
Public gardens / Landscaping plans 0546
Public gardens / Master plans 0806, 0960
Public housing / Site plans 0042
Public land / Preliminary drawings 0943
Public parks / Landscaping plans 01183, 0547, 0563, 0903, 0994
Public parks / Master plans 0926
Public parks / Topographic maps 01004
Public schools / Landscaping plans 01227, 0537, 0689, 0690, 0917
Public schools / Site plans 0591
Public space / Landscaping plans 0625
Public spaces / Comprehensive plans 0717
Public spaces / Landscaping plans 01210, 0714, 0766, 0994
Public spaces / Master plans 0952
Quadrangles / Landscaping plans 01153
Railroad cars / Landscaping plans 0663
Ramps / Site plans 0299
Real estate development / Landscaping plans 0534
Real estate development / Site plans 05001
Real estate management / Landscaping plans 05029
Recreation areas / Landscaping plans 0858
Recreation areas / Master plans 0679, 0951, 0976
Recreation areas / Site plans 0872
Recreation areas / Topographic maps 01004
Regional parks / Comprehensive plans 0717
Regional parks / Master plans 0875
Religious buildings / Landscaping plans 0973
Remodeling / Architectural drawings 0143
Renovation / Site plans 0528
Renovations / Sketches 01226
Research buildings / Landscaping plans 0617
Research centers / Landscaping plans 01221, 0594
Research institutes / Landscaping plans 0424, 0613, 0883, 0931
Research laboratories / Landscaping plans 0508, 0594
Research libraries / Architectural drawings 0677
Research libraries / Landscaping plans 0693
Residences / Landscape plans 0989
Residences / Landscaping plans 0977
Resorts / Landscaping plans 01248, 05028
Resorts / Master plans 0914, 0944
Resorts / Preliminary drawings 0515
Retail stores / Landscaping plans 0540
Riverbanks / Site plans 01233
Riverfronts / Landscaping plans 01062, 0134
Riverfronts / Master plans 0875
Riverfronts / Municipal plans 01011
River fronts / Landscaping plans 01060
Rivers / Landscaping plans 0908
Rivers / Master plans 0679, 0875
Rivers / Site plans 01233
River towns / Master plans 0845
Roads / Landscaping plans 0635, 0984
Roads / Site plans 0928
Roadside improvements / Landscaping plans 0957
Roadside improvements / Working drawings 0535
Roofs / Detail drawings 05011, 05013
Sailboats / Architectural drawings 05040
Schematic drawings / Comprehensive plans 0717
Schools / Landscaping plans 0610
Schoolyards / Landscaping plans 0537
Scientic societies / Landscaping plans 0437
Scientific societies / Landscaping plans 0581, 0638
Sculpture gardens / Landscaping plans 01074, 01106, 01159
Sculpture gardens / Preliminary drawings 01032
Secret societies / Landscaping plans 0541
Security / Landscaping plans 0597
Seminaries / Landscaping plans 01109
Senior centers / Landscaping plans 01221
Settlement houses / Landscaping plans 0530
Shopping centers / Landscaping plans 05034, 0540, 0887, 0922
Shopping centers / Master plans 0879
Shopping malls / Site plans 0738
Shopping plazas / Landscaping plans 0540
Shores (Landforms) / Master plans 01119
Single family dwellings / Landscaping plans 0918
Single-family dwellings / Landscaping plans 0009, 0915
Ski lodges / Landscaping plans 0445
Ski lodges / Plans (Drawings) 01014
Ski resorts / Landscaping plans 01071, 05042, 0671, 0858
Ski resorts / Landscaping plans 0481
Ski resorts / Regional plans 0735
Ski resorts / Site plans 01024, 0702, 0747, 0872, 0969
Ski trails / Site plans 0702
Slides (Recreation equipment) / Site plans 0299
Social services / Landscaping plans 0853
Spas / Master plans 0944
Special libraries / Landscaping plans 01191
Special libraries / Preliminary drawings 0523
Sports and recreation areas / Site plans 0852
Sports complexes / Landscaping plans 01155, 05030
Sports complexes / Site plans 0702
Squares / Competition drawings 01176
Squares (Open spaces) / Landscaping plans 01160, 0714
Stadiums / Landscaping plans 05035
State capitols / Competition drawings 01223
State government / Landscaping plans 05045
State parks / Master plans 0811
State parks / Site maps 05016a
State universities / Landscaping plans 0881, 0886, 0904
State universities / Master plans 01252
Storage facilities / Landscaping plans 0934
Streetscapes / Landscaping plans 01164
Student housing / Landscaping plans 01085
Student unions / Landscaping plans 0555, 0924
Subdivisions / Landscaping plans 01183
Suburban houses / Site plans 0332
Suburban landscapes / Site plans 0332
Summer camps / Landscaping plans 0659
Summer resorts / Landscaping plans 0671
Teaching hospitals / Landscaping plans 0803
Technology / Landscaping plans 0660
Telephone exchanges / Landscaping plans 0950
Terraces / Sketches 01226
Terraces (Landscaped-site elements) / Planting plans 0536
Theaters / Landscaping plans 0661
Theaters / Preliminary drawings 0733
Theological seminaries / Landscaping plans 01085
Theological seminaries / Master plans 0398
Theological seminaries / Preliminary drawings 0523
Tourism / Master plans 0811
Towers / Site plans 0738
Townhouses / Landscaping plans 05020
Towns / Master plans 0845
Tract houses / Site plans 0332
Trade unions / Landscaping plans 0656
Traffic / Landscaping plans 0691
Traffic / Site plans 0701
Traffic / Working drawings 0535
Traffic circles / Landscaping plans 0646
Traffic engineering / Landscaping plans 0675
Traffic engineering / Master plans 0861
Traffic engineering / Working drawings 0535
Transportation complexes / Landscaping plans 0843
Trust companies / Landscaping plans 0607
Universities / Landscapinge plans 05036
Universities / Landscaping plans 0553, 0555, 0582, 0599, 0600, 0601, 0613, 0617, 0619, 0621, 0634, 0635, 0650, 0678, 0724, 0729, 0754, 0759, 0803, 0825, 0839, 0840, 0883, 0886, 0904, 0931
Universities / Master plans 01100, 0570, 0583, 0807
Universities / Planting plans 0694
Universities / Site plans 0692, 0702, 0741
Universities (Institutions) / Master plans 0715
Universities and colleges / Landscaping plans 0441, 0775, 0788, 0795, 0921
Universities and colleges / Master plans 0486, 0487
Universities and colleges / Site plans 0383
Urban areas / Site plans 0734, 0876
Urban beautification / Landscaping plans 0691
Urban beautification. / Landscaping plans 01164
Urban centers / Landscaping plans 0887
Urban centers / Master plans 0879
Urban design / Landscaping plans 01156, 01210, 01297, 0138, 0636, 0646
Urban design / Master plans 01171, 0498, 0913
Urban design / Plans (Drawings) 01092, 01093
Urban design / Site plans 0528, 0876
Urban design / Working drawings 0535
Urban development / Design development drawings 01184
Urban development / Master plans 01186
Urban development / Site plans 0734
Urban developments / Landscaping plans 01264
Urban environments / Site plans 0738
Urban landscapes / Landscaping plans 01266, 0424, 0613, 0636, 0691
Urban land use / Landscaping plans 01273
Urban parks / Competition drawings 01176
Urban parks / Comprehensive plans 0717
Urban parks / Design development drawings 01184
Urban parks / Landscaping plans 01062, 01079, 01160, 0506, 0547, 0563, 0625, 0655, 0681, 0682, 0684, 0686, 0721, 0725, 0726, 0800, 0962
Urban parks / Master plans 01025, 01119, 0951, 0954, 0976
Urban parks / Site plans 0730, 0746, 0773
Urban planning / Landscaping plans 0885
Urban planning / Master plans 0216
Urban renewal / Master plans 0913
Urban universities / Landscapinge plans 05036
Urban universities / Landscaping plans 01280, 0441, 0613, 0883, 0924, 0931
Utilities buildings / Landscaping plans 0950
Vacation houses / Architectural drawings 0817
Valleys / Landscaping plans 0908
Vents (Outlets) / Planting plans 0459
Vermont: Shelburne: Bostwick Property / Landscaping plans 01145
Walkways / Site plans 01022
Warehouses / Landscaping plans 0720
Waterfronts / Landscaping plans 01273, 01297, 0721, 0723
Waterfronts / Master plans 0913
Waterfront spaces / Landscaping plans 01273
Water gardens / Landscaping plans 01062
Water gardens / Preliminary drawings 01095
Water quality management / Landscaping plans 0589
Watersheds / Landscaping plans 0908
Watersheds / Master plans 0679
Water treatment plants / Landscaping plans 0589
Waterways / Master plans 0816
Welfare buildings / Landscaping plans 0476
Winter gardens / Landscaping plans 01191
Winter resorts / Landscaping plans 01071, 0445, 05042, 0671, 0858
Winter resorts / Master plans 0914
Winter resorts / Plans (Drawings) 01014
Winter resorts / Regional plans 0735
Winter resorts / Site plans 01024, 0747, 0865, 0969
Working drawings / Landscaping plans 0661
Working drawings / Plans (Drawings) 05004
World trade centers / Landscaping plans 01212
Yacht clubs / Landscaping plans 05028
Zoos / Site plans 0730
Zoos / Survey plans 0819